regencymovies.com 2019-04-11

# Regencymovies.com Privacy Policy

Regency Theatres respects your right to the privacy of the personal information you provide us on our Web site. To that end, any personal information you provide to us via Regencymovies.com will be known only to two parties: you and Regency Theatres. The only exception to this rule is when you make a purchase on our web site and we are required to provide information to the payment processor to confirm your identity. The following policy is intended to explain how your personal information will be treated as you make use of our site and its features. Personal information includes your name, street and e-mail addresses, billing information, and any other personal information you may provide here.

**Traffic data  
** Each time a visitor comes to the Regencymovies.com site, our servers -- like most on the Web -- collect some basic technical information, including, for example, the visitor's domain name (e.g., whether the user is logged on from aol.com or whitehouse.gov), referral data (e.g., we record the address of the last URL a user visited prior to clicking through to a RegencyMovies.com Web site) and browser and platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform). We also count, track and aggregate the visitor's activity into our analysis of general traffic flows at our sites (e.g. tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the Regencymovies.com site, etc.). To these ends, we may merge information about visitors and visits into group data but we will not disclose your individual identity or personally identifiable data without your permission. When we do present aggregated information to outside companies, no one will be able to identify you or contact you.

**Use of Regencymovies.com cookies  
** A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies in a limited way to help customize your Regencymovies.com experience—for example to identify your "home" theater—and to identify unique browsers that visit us and to track usage throughout our site. The information about user behavior that Regency Theatres collects through cookies is aggregated into general reports how customers use our web site and not tied to individual identities, with one exception. If you log in to our site and make a purchase, your purchase history is tied to the identity you've created on our site, which is in turn identified by the cookie on your computer. This just means that you won't have to enter your name and address each time you want to make a purchase or contact us about something; rest assured that no one will be able to access that information without providing a password which you define and have the power to change any time you like.

**Login & Profile Information on Regencymovies.com**  
Our site may provide you with the opportunity to log in and customize some features of our site. As with all information you provide, this information will be protected under accepted security protocols and not provided to any third parties.

**Providing personal financial information to Regencymovies.com  
** This site will soon allow you to purchase gift certificates and make reservations for special events on line. When you do so, please be aware that your credit card information will be stored in our database for a period of 1-15 hours, depending on when your purchase is made. As soon as possible, Regency staff will record your reservation, charge your credit card, and delete the information from our servers. Before this is done, your information is protected by secure sockets layers (SSL) technology and encrypted so that it is as protected as possible from any outside person gaining access. Beyond these precautions, Regencymovies.com makes no guarantee and provides no surety for your online transactions.

| Very often, your credit card company protects you when you make purchases online, and you should always make sure that any page where you enter your credit card information is protected by this symbol: |   
---|---  
  
If you would like to remove your name and e-mail address from our database, you can send an e-mail requesting removal by using the link below.

**Shipping & Handling**  
Please allow Regency Theatres 24-48 hours to process gift card orders to ship out. You have the option of choosing USPS priority mail or Fedex. Costs for shipping will vary.

**Refunds**  
All sales are final, and no refunds will be given.

**Other sites**  
Regencymovies.com contains links to other sites on the Web. We cannot control and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other Web sites.

**Who can I ask if I have any additional questions?**  
If you have any further questions or concerns about Regency Theatres privacy policy and use of personal information, please use our feedback form or link below to send us an email.
